P1:
Part(b)
break 14
break 8

Part(c)
1. Because the for loop in factorial function starts with i = 0, as num *=i, this will make num = 0, as num is in the function condition
   i<=num, the loop stop and never goes to 2nd loop
2. 
   r
   break 8
   break 14
   c
   c
   c
   c
   c
   from gdb it's clear that for each num the breakpoint in factorial within the loop only been reached once
   
Part(d)
1. Because the num is updated, in this case it's enlarging during the loop, since it's also in the function
   condition, the loop won't stop at the desired value num, and also this function doesn't has a return value statement
2. 
   r
   break 8
   c
   c
   c
   ....(keep continue)
   from gdb it's clear that num keep increasing

P4:
size is Θ(constant)
It's only returning a variable so just one step

insert is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the position is specified right before the tail, the function needs to
iterate (n-1) times during the loop, so Θ(n)

remove is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the position is specified right before the tail, the function needs to 
iterate (n-1) times during the loop, so Θ(n)

set is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the position is specified right before the tail, the function needs to 
iterate (n-1) times during the loop, so Θ(n)

get is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the position is specified right before the tail, the function needs to 
iterate (n-1) times during the loop, so Θ(n)

P6:
size is Θ(constant)
It's only returning a variable so just one step

add is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the input email is not a duplicate in the list, the function needs to 
iterate n times during the loop to determine there's no same emails exist, so Θ(n)

remove is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the target is at the end of the list, the functions needs to iterate 
n times during the loop to match the key for delete, so Θ(n)

get is Θ(n)
In the worst case, when the target is at the end of the list, the functions needs to iterate
n times during the loop to macth the key, so Θ(n)